regularlabs.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer - Regular Labs

This privacy policy sets out how Regular Labs uses and protects any information that you give Regular Labs when you use this website. When visiting www.regularlabs.com the site records on behalf of Regular Labs personal and extra data for internal record keeping. Regular Labs may use the information to improve our products and services.

_**We will never share your details with any third parties.**_

Regular Labs is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Storing of personal data

### The GDPR

_The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679 is a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all individuals within the European Union. It also addresses the export of personal data outside the EU. The GDPR aims primarily to give control to citizens and residents over their personal data and to simplify the regulatory environment for international business by unifying the regulation within the EU.  
It was adopted on 14 April 2016, and became enforceable on 25 May 2018._

Personal data refers to any information related to you (or your company), that can be used to directly or indirectly identify you.

Here is an overview of the different types of personal data Regular Labs collects and stores. It also describes the reason why this data is stored and for how long.

### Login data

When you create an account on www.regularlabs.com, the information you provide will be stored in our database.

**What is stored?**

  * Your name
  * Your username
  * Your email address

**Why is it stored?**

This data is required to be able to let you log in to the website.

**How long is it stored?**

This data will be kept as long as you regularly log in. Inactive accounts (have not logged in for 5 years or longer) will be removed during a yearly cleanup.

**Can it be removed?**

If you want your account to be removed, you can send your request to   
But please note that this will also disable any active Regular Labs subscriptions that are connected to your account.  
You will also no longer be able to use other services on www.regularlabs.com like the support forum.

### Purchase data

When you make a purchase on www.regularlabs.com (buy a subscription) we will store the required data you provide to us.

**What is stored?**

  * Your name
  * Your address
  * Your email address
  * Your PayPal email address (if applicable)
  * Your phone number (optional)
  * Your company name (optional)
  * Your VIES registration number (optional)
  * Your IP address

The payment itself is done via PayPal. This means no personal payment data (like credit card information) except your PayPal email address is stored on our database.

**Why is it stored?**

This data is used to create invoices. This data is required for tax purposes.

**How long is it stored?**

The national tax authorities (in The Netherlands) require us to keep this data for 7 years. After that, the data will be removed during a yearly cleanup.

**Can it be removed?**

No, you can not request this data to be removed from our database.  
The national tax authorities (in The Netherlands) require us to keep this data for 7 years. These national laws overrule the GDPR law.

### Download data

When you download extensions you have access to through your subscription on www.regularlabs.com we will store some extra data.

**What is stored?**

  * The used id (which is connected to your account)
  * The Download Key used (which is connected to your account)
  * Your IP address

**Why is it stored?**

This data is used for internal use only. It helps us solve any issues that might come up when downloads fail. It also helps us keep track of and prevent any abuse to our download systems.

**How long is it stored?**

This data is stored for 5 years. After that, the data will be removed during a yearly cleanup.

**Can it be removed?**

If you want this data to be removed, you can send your request to   
But please note that this will also disable any active Regular Labs subscriptions that are connected to your account.

### Analytical data

The www.regularlabs.com website uses Google Analytics. This is set up to only store [anonymized data](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en).  
This means that neither your exact IP addres or any other personal data is stored.

### Location of Data

Our website and database run on servers controlled by the hosting company SiteGround.  
The servers are located in Amsterdam (The Netherlands, Europe).

SiteGround is GDPR compliant through the [Data Processing Agreement](https://www.siteground.com/term/301.htm?scid=3&lang=en) we have with them.

While Regular Labs makes every effort to ensure that the content of this website is accurate, the website is provided 'as is' and Regular Labs makes no representations or warranties in relation to the accuracy or completeness of the information found on it. While the content of www.regularlabs.com is provided with the utmost care and attention, we do not warrant that the information will always be up to date, be true and not misleading, or that this site will always (or ever) be available for use.

We do not warrant that the servers that make this website available will be error, virus or bug free and you accept that it is your responsibility to make adequate provision for protection against such threats. We recommend scanning any files before downloading.

Nothing on this website should be taken to constitute professional advice or a formal recommendation and we exclude all representations and warranties relating to the content and use of this site. In no event will Regular Labs be liable for any incidental, indirect, consequential or special damages of any kind, or any damages whatsoever, including, without limitation, those resulting from loss of profit, loss of contracts, goodwill, data, information, income, anticipated savings or business relationships, whether or not advised of the possibility of such damage, arising out of or in connection with the use of this website or any linked websites.

%MCEPASTEBIN%
